pcmonitors.info 2017-10-02

# Privacy Policy and Cookies | PC Monitors

**If you wish to disable cookies you may do so through your individual browser options**. This action will apply universally and not just to those collected from your visit to our website. More detailed information about cookie management specific to various web browsers can be found on [aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/). Specific information on the cookies our website uses and how to control them individually can be found below.

Last updated: March 27th 2017  
  
At PCMonitors.info, the privacy of our visitors is of paramount importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected by us and how it is used. If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy please feel free to [email](mailto:adamsi@pcmonitors.info?subject=Privacy%20Policy) Adam Simmons, the Chief Administrator of the website.

## Log Files

As is common practice PCMonitors.info makes use of **log files from Google Analytics**. The information inside the log files includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, Internet Service Provider (ISP), browser type, date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyse trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. If you would not like your usage to be tracked in this way it is possible to [opt out of Google Analytics](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=None) and prevent tracking cookies being placed on your computer.

## Other Cookies

In addition to Google’s tracking cookies PCMonitors.info will place **temporary session identification cookies** on your computer if you log into the website to post on the forum or leave a comment. These are non-tracking cookies which we have no access to – they do not send any information to us or any third party. They are used purely to allow you to access the forums or to post comments without re-entering details such as your ‘post as’ name and anything else you typed into the comment form.

As explained in the subsequent section (affiliations), PCMonitors.info provides **links through to Amazon** in select posts, reviews and the recommendations section. These cookies automatically expire after 24 hours, and no personal information is gathered. The purpose of these cookies from our point of view is to allow Amazon to track any purchases you make after following any of the affiliate links on our website. This ensures that we are given any commission that is due.

PCMonitors.info has no access to or control over these third-party cookies and we are not able to see any personally identifiable information. [Further information on Amazon’s cookies can be found on this page](http://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html/ref=footer_privacy?ie=UTF8&nodeId=468496).  

## Affiliations

Our advertising partners use cookies to track visitor activity. Our current affiliations are as follows:

**Amazon.co.uk/.de/.fr/.it/.es: Adam Simmons of PCMonitors.info is a participant in the Amazon Europe S.à.r.l. Associates Programme, an affiliate advertising programme designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.co.uk/.de/.fr/.it/.es.**

**Amazon.ca: Adam Simmons of PCMonitors.info is a participant in the Amazon.com.ca, Inc. Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.ca.**

**Amazon.com: Adam Simmons of PCMonitors.info is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.com.**

We choose to be affiliated with this company for many reasons including the range and prices of current monitors and helpful user reviews. Perhaps the most important reason, however, is their excellent customer service and returns policy. Many people will be familiar with this company and will already have an account with them.

If you follow any link through to Amazon from our website and complete your purchase within 24 hours we will receive a small commission.  We really do appreciate any purchases you make via our website as it is a great way to say thank you for the considerable amount of time and effort that we spend on it and will encourage further growth of this resource. We also appreciate the kind words many have expressed through email contact, the forum and elsewhere. Thank you for your support.
